If you're ever in Kinosaki Onsen, then
you should definitely consider staying
at this Ryokan. Our room was [music] a
traditional Japanese style room with
tatami floors. Everything just looked
intentional and elegant.
It even came with an open-air bath that
we absolutely loved during our stay.
But arguably the best part of staying
here was the chance to book [music] a
private Onsen experience exclusive to
hotel guests.
It was honestly [music] the most
beautiful private Onsen I've ever
experienced and it ended up being the
highlight of our trip.
One of the perks of staying at a Ryokan
is getting to experience a Kaiseki
dinner, a Japanese multi-course [music]
meal served right in your room. Seasonal
specialties include Matsuba snow crab
and the locally [music] prized Tajima
beef.
After dinner, we head out for an evening
[music] stroll to visit the famous
public Onsens. Hotel guests receive an
Onsen [music] pass that gives you a free
access to all seven bathhouses, the
perfect way to end the night in
Kinosaki.